On the way back home, I stopped by the
good old Hamon family restaurantKAGEya.
To celebrate Julia's graduation from
high school,
Enoshima Kamakura High School students
Gumi date!
Yay!
I wanted to do this!
I said I wanted to do something in
school uniform, and my dream came true!
I fell!
That's right!
I can't believe the sea is beautiful!
Let's go!
Go!
Hello!
Today
What are we doing today?
We are a JK combo
We are going to visit Kamakura
It's a VLOG!
I'm so excited!
I've never done this outside before
I'm so happy!
I'm going to roll the rope
I thought it would be nice if I could
take the rope off
But I couldn't take the rope off
I'm a bad JK!
That's not true!
There's a hole in the seat
I'm a bad JK
I'm going to do my best!
The background doesn't look like
Kamakura, so I'll go this way
There's a lot of fortune!
I'm going to sell it!
I think there are a lot of delicious
things in Kamakura, so I'd like to go
eat it right away!
Let's go!
It's bread!
Raw bread
There are a lot of tea-related things
I know this
I know this!
I've seen it before!
It's a straw-shaped rice cake!
Have you ever been to Kamakura?
I've heard the name of Kamakura
It's my first time here
I'm going to eat it!
I did it with straight iron.
Wow!
Isn't it great?
Your bangs are beautiful.
I'm good at this part, but I'm not good
at this part.
I have it.
I'm going to curl it.
I'm happy.
Wow, it's a bomb.
Wow.
It's a bomb.
I'm happy.
I'm eating raw fish in front of me.
There's something inside.
I'm eating Kenchin-jiru.
What is Kamakura?
I was talking about Kamakura yesterday.
I was wondering if it was pasta.
You were talking about pasta.
I was talking about pasta.
There are many restaurants.
I was looking at sashimi.
There were seafood and cuttlefish.
There are many things.
I found a toy that Hiyorin was playing
with.
This is my toy.
I wanted this, too.
Didn't Hiyorin play with this?
She did.
How many toys did she get?
This is a toy.
There are many things.
Let's ask the staff about the fortune-
telling of love.
I'll take a picture.
Oh, you take a picture like that.
I'll take a picture of Miyazaki.
I saw her at the beginning.
Let's start with Julia.
I'll open it.
Why?
It's karaoke.
Today's lucky spot is karaoke.
You'll be disturbed as long as you're
going well.
Don't worry about it.
It's a lucky spot for Noriko.
Today's lucky spot is 2.
Julia's lucky spot is 2.
Oh, I see.
This camera is also written 2.
It's a sticker.
It may be good.
Do you realize your charm?
I don't know if it's good.
Next is Aki.
I'll take a picture of the star of the
year.
I'm the first one to take a picture of
the star of the year.
Really?
I'll take a picture.
It's a heart sticker.
It's 1.
If you have a strong will and act,
you'll be fine.
Be yourself.
Today's lucky spot is a library.
I don't go to the library.
Wait.
It says there are 5 lucky spots.
Isn't it amazing?
Why?
Have the courage to take a step
forward.
I see.
I think there's a good thing.
The number is...
2, 5.
I'll tie it.
You should tie it.
I'll tie it from Julia.
It's a good feeling.
Look. There are many voices of people.
I'm going to eat them.
I've started!
I hope it's good.
Is it whitebait?
It's raw!
I wanted to eat whitebait.
Have you ever eaten raw?
Yes, I have.
You haven't?
Whitebait, whitebait, whitebait, baby,
whitebait.
When I was on the train to Kamakura, I
took a video of the Instagrammable
competition.
I was drinking a tea with a tea leaf.
I thought it was a good way to drink.
It's good to shoot outside.
I'm excited.
Did you always do nothing when you were
in school?
I'm in the third grade, so I'll get my
hair done.
I always have cute hair when I'm in the
first grade.
I used to make dumplings and twintails
when I was in the first grade.
I've become an adult.
I used to go to a hair salon, but I
don't remember the name.
JKRR
First place!
I used to fold my skirt.
I used to tie my bangs.
I don't know if this is JKRR, but I
used to roll my hair and apply for a
hair roll.
I don't know if you saw it, but I used
to do it.
I'm going to eat raw white rice bowl.
I've never eaten raw white rice bowl.
I'm looking forward to eating it.
Let's go!
We are in the restaurant.
Thank you for your viewing.
What are you doing?
This is the second time we eat out.
We ate pasta once.
We ate it.
We ate sweet potato pasta.
This is the second time.
I didn't know that we would go to the
swimming pool.
I was thinking about going to the pool.
I'm glad we came here.
We will go to the swimming pool.
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
I'll start with the egg.
Let's eat!
It's like eating a hot spring egg.
It's jiggly.
The white part is...
I recently started eating this.
Is it ginger?
No, it's raw white.
Oh, it's raw white.
It's a crow.
Is it a fish?
It's a giraffe.
I don't know.
We ate raw whitebait rice bowl.
It was delicious.
The ginger on the rice was delicious.
I love shiso.
We ate raw whitebait rice bowl and
fried fish.
It was delicious.
This is the first time to eat whitebait
rice bowl in a half year.
I ate it after a long time.
We ate it.
It was delicious.
I'm going to ride a human train now.
It's my first time to ride a human
train.
I've never ridden a train before.
I remember I rode a train when I was a
child.
I'm so lonely.
Can you see me?
Can you hear me?
The train is coming.
I'm going to ride a train.
Wow!
I'm in the roof!
Please hold the rope.
I'm holding it.
I'm scared.
I'm going to do it.
I'm a little scared.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of the back.
I'm going to jump on the roof.
I'm running.
I'm scared.
How many kilograms are you?
I'm sure.
You are 100kg.
You are heavy.
I'm sure.
I'm Tamakura.
I'm Tamakura Tamura.
I'm Riku Hatsujo.
Do you have any memories of high
school?
The first one is the cultural festival.
It was the time when the rainbow
project was popular.
We did it together.
I danced to the special dance.
We made it together.
It was a great memory.
It was fun.
High school.
I'm graduating soon, so I'm happy to be
a member of the school's last memory.
Look at the bridge.
The river is beautiful.
I feel the bridge.
My hammock is so thin.
We're not there yet.
But we aren't so old, so it'll come to
us.
It should.
It's a surface auger.
Yeah.
In our brain
I can't imagine Kanamin and Oharu-chan
being here.
I can't imagine it.
I can't imagine it at all.
I've never seen Kanamin, Hiyorin, and
Oharu-chan in school uniforms.
I've seen Nishita-chan a few times.
I've seen Hiyori once.
I've never seen her.
I've never seen them in school
uniforms.
I can't imagine it.
But I saw you studying Japanese during
the test.
I thought you were amazing.
I can imagine how you felt.
I thought you were amazing. You did it
so well.
I thought you were amazing.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
There are many kinds of clothes.
There is a rental shop.
I went to Asakusa last time.
I want to go to Asakusa.
I want to visit Asakusa.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
We went to the castle.
We came to Asakusa!
I want to come to Kamakura again.
There are many shops around here.
I want to eat a lot.
It's youth.
Cherry blossoms are falling.
Enjoy JK.
One more year.
Thank you.
What should I do?
I think we're done.
We're back!
It was so fun!
I didn't expect to take a picture and
come back.
It was so nice.
It was a dream to take a picture with a
school uniform.
I wanted to do it, so I'm glad.
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
I got a sticker!
If you collect this in spring and
autumn,
I heard there's something good.
You can get a t-shirt with a doll or a
Kamakura on the back.
I'd like to ride it again.
I'll put Nare next to me next time.
Let's line up in three cars.
I got a lot of pictures taken.
I wonder if I'll ride this car.
Let's take a picture.
It's like this.
It's good. It's like youth.
It's youth.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thanks for watching!
Bye bye!
We came to Yurigahama by Enoden!
Isn't it nice to have a break?
I haven't seen a break recently.
Really?
I'm a little bit sick of it.
I agree.
There is a shop in this town.
I feel good.
It's been a while since we did a
photoshoot.
That's right.
Then, let's do it like that.
It's getting warmer than that time.
It's just the right temperature.
It's getting warmer.
My nose is getting red.
It's nice.
We have a villa in a place like this.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I feel like I'm in Ghibli.
It's like a memory.
Are you done?
I'm done.
I'm going home today.
Wow, there's a surfboard.
There's a lot of people lining up.
Have you ever surfed?
No.
I've seen a necrogirl surfing.
Oh, really?
I want to go to the sea.
I'm cold, but I can do it.
I used to go to the sea every year.
I remember you said you ate shellfish.
I used to do salt-grilled clams.
I've done it once.
I can see the sea.
I feel like I've been there by car.
I remember the road I passed once.
Look at this.
The sea is beautiful.
It's a sand beach.
This is amazing.
I haven't felt this for a long time.
It's soft and smooth.
I've never been to the sea.
It's nice.
There are many different kinds of
seaweeds.
We've arrived at the sea.
It's quite hard.
Some people are swimming.
I think so.
I feel a little cold.
Surfing!
Can I stand up?
I did it!
I'm rowing.
You're rowing.
It's great.
The ship is nice.
I'm rowing.
I wrote it down.
What is this?
Ahhhhhh oh no!
Thank you for watching.
I'm so happy!
Look!
The sea is so beautiful!
My feet are wet.
I remember the rainy day when I went to
high school.
Congratulations on your graduation!
Thank you!
Congratulations!
I'm going to the beach.
Umm... If the landed on my hands next
time...
Hi accordingly...
Uhh!
Umm...
Ahh!
Ahhh!
ALL DAY EVERY NIGHT!
Thank you.
I don't know what's going on.
I can see it!
I did it!
Is there a pattern that this doesn't
disappear?
It's left a little far away.
Oh, it's coming.
It's OK.
Come here.
It's coming.
I can't see it.
Thank you for watching.
The day of the final screening
Yay!
So, we've been enjoying the summer
vacation.
It was fun.
It was a good memory.
As a J.K.Covey, we were able to enjoy a
lot of things at J.K.
Yay!
It's the best memory.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to graduate.
Congratulations!
Congratulations to the high school
students!
J.K.!
Yay!
If you enjoyed this video and enjoyed
the feeling of youth,
please subscribe to our channel and
click the good button!
Please look forward to our new song!
Thank you for watching!
I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'll
try.
I'll try to do my best.